

Louky Schutte Singel 437, 1012WP, Amsterdam | +31629007827 | loukyschutte@live.nl

As an ambitious Econometrics undergraduate and a competitive rower I learned to achieve my goals by practicing discipline and good structure. I thrive when I'm being challenged. I am committed to solving complex real world problems by using data-analysis and computer models.

EDUCATION & QUALIFICATIONS

2020	CS50's Introduction to Computer Science: <i>Topics include abstraction, algorithms, data structures, encapsulation, resource management, security, and software engineering. Languages include C, Python, and SQL, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.</i>
2019	Data Science: Machine Learning, a course of study offered by HarvardX, an online learning initiative of Harvard University. Credential URL: https://courses.edx.org/certificates/8267761226f9408592fbefc8fed6d59c
July 2019	Summer Course Engineering and Social Entrepreneurship, <i>Kings College London</i> .
2016 - 2019	Bachelor Econometrics and Operational Research, Minor Risk Management for Financial institutions, average grade: 8.0 (/10) Thesis: Network simulation of frailty and ageing http://www.ubvu.vu.nl/pub/fulltext/scripties/27 2603804 0.pdf Amsterdam, Vrije Universiteit
2009 - 2015	High School, Gymnasium, Zeist, KSG de Breul
2013 - 2015	Extracurricular, Cambridge English Proficiency (CPE), Zeist, KSG de Breul
2013 - 2016	Extracurricular, U-talent academy, Utrecht, <i>University of Utrecht</i> In-depth program for the courses mathematics, science, biology and physics

CAREER SUMMARY

October 2018 – March 2020

Operational Risk Manager, *Anthos Private Wealth Management*, Amsterdam

Providing value to the Board members by evaluating and managing operational risks. Exhibiting a strong sense of responsibility and involving employees in projects that minimize risk and ensure compliance with regulatory requirements.

September 2012 – July 2019

Tutor, *university and high school students,* Operational Research and Mathematics, Amsterdam

 Helping students to plan, study and pass exams, increasing confidence in their own abilities.

June 2015 -August 2015

Camp counsellor, Camp Letts (CCUSA), Edgewater MD

• Taking care of a group of twelve children aged 8 to 10, teaching sailing, working together with international colleagues.

September 2010 - July 2015

Member of the Student Council, KSG de Breul, Zeist

- · Participated in the Comenius School Partnership, a student exchange program in the EU.
- · Contributing to a beneficent collaboration of students and teachers by attending meetings and conducting surveys.

SKILLS

Fluent in Dutch and English

Programming in C, Java, Python, R, SQL, and Ox

Web development with HTML, CSS, Python and Javascript

Documentation in Excel and LaTeX

Understanding of concepts in analysis, probability theory, finance, operations research, mathematical economics and numerical methods.

ACTIVITIES

Member of the women's lightweight crew '18 of a competitive rowing club in Amsterdam.

Medical Data Science Meetups

Outside sports such as hiking, running, biking, mountain biking, sailing and kite-surfing

Longest bike tour: 170 km, around Markermeer